CONTACT



2 623 21 06 46



angelalonso223@gmail.com



 Av. Doctor Rico, 21 03005 Alicante, Spain



in angelalonsop

ABOUT ME

Telematics student interested in both software and web application development. I have a great ability to adapt to all kinds of environments. I always give the best of myself. What sets me apart is my ability to work as part of a team and my enthusiasm for learning and developing my skills. I am always on the lookout for opportunities for further learning and experience.

CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco Academy

- CCNA: Introduction to Networks (2020)
- · CCNA: Switching, Routing, and Wireless Essentials (2023)
- · CCNA: Enterprise Networking, Security, and Automation (2023)

SKILLS

- Software Development
- Web Development
- Java Programming
- · Problem-Solving
- C ++ and C

LANGUAGES

- Spanish | Native
- English | Intermediate
- Catalan | Intermediate



TELEMATICS ENGINEER

EXPERIENCE

APPLICATION CONSULTANT

Capgemini España, S.L

Dec 2023 - May 2024

- Collaborated with development team to customize applications to meet client requirements.
- Provided technical support and troubleshooting for application issues to ensure client satisfaction.

MONITOR OF RECREATION AND FREE TIME

Asociación La Forja

Jun 2022 - Present

- · Led and organized recreational activities for groups of all ages and abilities.
- · Promotion of values such as respect, tolerance and coexistence among the campers.

KITCHEN ASSISTANT

Asociación La Forja

Jun 2020 - Aug 2022

- Maintained cleanliness and organization of kitchen equipment and work stations.
- Collaborated with team members to ensure timely and accurate food service.

EDUCATION

MASTER'S DEGREE IN SOFTWARE SYSTEMS ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY

University Polytechnic of Valencia

Sep 2024 - Present

DEGREE IN TELEMATICS ENGINEERING

University of Valencia

Sep 2020 - Sep 2024

• Honors in several subjects related to programming. electronics and networks.

ELEMENTARY AND PROFESSIONAL DEGREE ON MUSIC

Conservatory of Music and Dance "Vicente Lillo Cánovas" Sep 2011 - May 2018